Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Publications Collection, 1887-2005 RL.00741
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
La Inversion Publicitaria en España boxes IO10, IO11
La Investigación Publicitaria en la Agencia, box IO11
La Lettre d'Information Media box IO4
Laboratory of Advertising Performance box SR5
Landsdowne boxes OV6, SR5
Landsdowne Marketing Limited box OV6
Latin American Markets box DG13
Leadership at JWT box DG18
Let's Try for That Extra 10% box DG12
L'Equipe box IO12 (RESTRICTED)
Lettre Ouverte box IO2
L'etude du Marche box IO2
Lexicon box DG21
Lexington International box SR5
LGFE box OV7
Liberation box IL9 (RESTRICTED)
Lidov Mural box OV1
Lifestages box DG21
Lining Up for Launch Day box IO9
Lippold Sculpture Construction box DO2
List of Accounts (London) box IL7
Lo Sviluppo di Nuove Marche box IO7
Look at 15-Second Commercials in the 90s, box DG22
Looking Forward to the Next 10 Years box DG22
Looking Up at JWT box DG23 (RESTRICTED)
Lord and Thomas Creeds box DG15
Magazine Audience Estimates box SR5
Major Market Index Plan box SR5
Making the Partnership Work box SR6 (RESTRICTED)
Management Performance and Evaluation box DG20
Management Philosophy box IO2
Management Reference Center Chronological Bibliography box DG21
Managers Meeting box IO3
Managing a JWT Office for Performance and Profit box DG18
Managing the Agency box DG27 (RESTRICTED)
Manchester box IL10
Manual of TV Basics box DG14
Manual Operativo para Cuentas box IO12 (RESTRICTED)
Many Worlds of S. Meek box DG19
Map and Guide of European Cities box IO3
Market Analysis of the 1931 Population Statistics for Great Britain and Ireland box IL1
Market Data box IO6
Market Potentials box DG11
Market Research and the Retailer box IL2
Market Research in Europe boxes SR2, SR4
Market Research on a European Basis box IL3, SR4
Market Sizes box IL5
Market Study for the Professional Nutritionist, box DO1
Marketing in a Defense Economy box DG11
Marketing In Crisis box IO12 (RESTRICTED)
Marketing Opportunities box DG11
Marketing Research box IO2
Marketing to Consumers box SR5
Markets Are Made of People box DG8
Markets to the North: Angola box IO10
Markets to the North: Belgian Congo box IO10
Markets to the North: British East Africa, box IO10
Markets to the North: General box IO10
Markets to the North: Mozambique or Portuguese East Africa box IO10
Markets to the North: Rhodesia and Nyasaland, box IO10
Markets to the North: South West Africa, box IO10
Marketwise box IO12 (RESTRICTED)
Measuring Self-Concept box SR1
Measuring the Audiences of Magazines box DG17, SR1
Media Digest--Europe boxes IL4, IL5
Media Information: Europe box DG17
Media Information (Germany) box IO12 (RESTRICTED)
Media Information--Switzerland box IO3
Media Information (U.S.) boxes DG17, DG18
Media Market in 1988 box IL10
Media Merchandising Services box DO2
Media Research Sources box DG26 (RESTRICTED)
Media: The New Creative Frontier? box DG21
Medical Journals box DG1
Memorandum and Introductory Package Regarding JWT's Transformation box DG26 (RESTRICTED)
Memorandum Regarding Five Speeches Presented at the JWT Fifth World Management Meeting box DG18
Merchandise Catalog box DO2
Merchandising Case History: Shell Premium With TCP box DG12
Merchandising of Food Products by Industry Co-Operatives box DG10
Merchant, Banker, Doctor box DG9
Mexican Market (Mexico) box IO7
Mexican Market (U.S.) box DG16
Mexican Mystique box DO2
México box DO3
Michigan Opera Theatre box DO4 (RESTRICTED)
Mil Novecientos setenta y nueve box IO11
Million Dollar Minute box DG20
Miracle Whip: I Couldn't Make It Without You! Cookbook box DG23 (RESTRICTED)
Mirror for a Lady box IL2
Mis Ajás Preferidos sobre Promoción box IO10
Mission Statement boxes DG19, DG22
Modern Advertising Agency Service box IO3
More Jobs than Men box DG10
Motor Racing Sponsorship: A Proposal for a Three-Country Survey box SR4
Moving Target box DG17
MRB International box SR5
Mysteries of Time and Space box IL7
Naget om JWT för og nu box OV4
National Creative Award box DG20
Network Sports Essentials box DG20
Net-Working: A Research Study on Employment and the Internet box DG25 (RESTRICTED)
New American Consumer box DG20
New Business Brochures box IL7
New Business Services box DG27 (RESTRICTED)
New Era in Ford Retailing box DG14
New Housewife box IL2
New Image Package box DG26 (RESTRICTED)
New JWT box IO1
New Map for Europe box IO3
New Media Explorers box DG19
New Medium: Television in the 1980s box DG18
New Office Announcement box IO3
New Premises for JWT Brussels box IO2
New Revolution in Distribution box DG15
New Visual Identity box DG26 (RESTRICTED)
New Wavelength box IL4
New York Office Guidebook box DO2
Newsletter (Hill & Knowlton) box SR4
No Están Todos Los Que Son, Pero Sí Son Todos Los Que Están box IO11
Notice to All Employees box IL6
O Público e a Propaganda box IO2
One Advertiser's Response to Pollution, Inflation, Shortages and Whatever's Next box DG17
One World of J. Walter Thompson Company: A Guide to 37 International Offices in 24 Countries box IL2
One World of Sam Meek box DG16
Open Letter to Our Cohorts at JWT box DG27 (RESTRICTED)
Operational Research and Marketing box IL2
Opportunities for American Manufacturers in Britain Today box IL1
Our Best Total Branding box DG26 (RESTRICTED)
Outline for An Advertising Agency Analysis, box IO3
Ouvre box IO12 (RESTRICTED)
Overview (South Africa) box IO10
P.T. Thomertwal Advertising box IO6
Pamphlet Collection box DG25 (RESTRICTED)
Pan-European Communication box IO2
Paper-Money Inflation in France: Where It Came from, What It Brought and How It Ended box DG9
Paradox Papers: Marketing in Modern Times, boxes DG22-DG26 (RESTRICTED)
Paradox Papers: Youth in the 90s box DG23 (RESTRICTED)
Partial Checklist of JWT Domestic Clients for Shopping Reference boxes DG23, DG26 (RESTRICTED)
Partners in the Marketing Revolution box DG17
Passion '03: JWT Europe, Middle East, Africa, box OV4
Passion 03: JWT Latinoamerica box OV5
Passion: North America box OV2
Passport to the North box IO3
People Buy Brands, Not Products boxes DG21, DG23, DG25 (RESTRICTED)
People's Use of Media box IL5
Perfil del Mercado Peruano box IO8
Performance Group box DO2
Peruvian Market box DG13
Peruvian Market Profile box IO8
Pet Food Market box DO2
Pharmaceutical Advertising and Marketing, box IL2
Philippine Market boxes DG13, IO9
Photo Engraving box DG11
Photo Engraving Processes box DG8
Photographic Essay box IO2
Pierre Caille box IO2
Pin-Pointing the Affluent Household box IL2
Plain Talk on Research box IO3
Plan for the Promotion of American Travel in Thailand box DG13
Plant City Advertising boxes DG10, DG11
Platform (Hill & Knowlton) box SR4
Plea for Education box DG10
Pocket Guide to Media Terms and Media Math, boxes DG20, DO1
Population and its Distribution boxes DG7-DG10, DG12, DG15
Population and Purchasing Power box DG10
Population Handbook of Great Britain and Ireland box DG8
Population Study box IO7
Portrait boxes IO4, OV4
Portuguese Grafitti box IO9
Portuguese Market box DG13
Positioning Advertising Copy Testing box SR5
Power of the Old, Shock of the New boxes DG24, DO4 (RESTRICTED), OV1A
PPGH/JWT Business Communications box IO8
PPGH/JWT in 15 Characteristics box IO8
PPGH/JWT Tien Jaar Merkenbeleid box IO8
PPGH/Moussault Werke box IO8
Practical Progress From A Theory of Adverstiments box IL5
Preliminary Report on the Present Pharmaceutical Situation and the Areas of Opportunity for Deltakos (Belgium) box SR4
Preparedness for Peace box DO1
Present Economic Conditions box DG8
Presentation Didn't Go Quite As We Expected..., box IL3
Presentation to Exxon Company box DG22
Press in Its Relation to Public Opinion and Government box DG9
Press Information (EA International) box OV6
Price Guarantees by Manufacturers with Sales Contracts box DO3
Primer for Post-War Prosperity box DG10
Primer of Capitalism Illustrated box DG10
Primetime Television Schedule: The Essentials, box DG20
Print Media Information box DG17
Private Label Reviewed box IL3
Prize Competition box DG8
Problem box IL10
Problem and Opportunity for Milk in California, box DG10
Problem Solvers box SR2
Product Information Booklet box SR5
Professional Development Handbook box DG24
Professional Development Programme box IO3
Professional Forum box DO2
Profit-Sharing and You box DG17
Project Enterprise box IO3
Project Norway box IL4
Propaganda (Brazil) box SR4
Proposal for a Series of Focus Groups on Birth Control Methods box SR4
Proposal: Corporate Communications/Jack Hilton, box DO1
Psychological Laboratory box SR2
Public Issues, Public Policy Group (Hill & Knowlton) box SR4
Publicidad en 1979 (Spain) box IO11
Publicité box IO2
Purchasing Power of the Consumer box DG8
Questions and Answers in Planning Advertising, box DO2
Radio: an Individual's Medium box DG15
Rapporto Annuale (JWT ITaly) box IO6
Read All About It! box IL4
Red Book/J. Walter Thompson Co. Advertising, box DG3
Red Ear box DG1
Reflections on an Agency/Peter Yeo box DG27 (RESTRICTED)
Regional and Split-Run Magazine Availabilities, box DG14
Relationship Between Purchasing Patterns and Advertising Exposure box IL3
Religious Press box DG1
Report on Advertising Agencies in the Far East, box IL2
Report on the Role of Radio in the Lives of American Housewives box DG14
Report on Private Label in U.S. Food Retailing, box IL2
Reports and Accounts (India) box IO5
Tesearch Audit of 1978 TGI box SR1
Research Audit of SMRB 1985 Study of Media and Markets box SR1
Research Department Role and Organization, box IO1
Research Development Procedures box IO1
Research Into Attitudes to Advertising box IL6
Resultattavlor box OV5
Results of 1977 Business/Financial Press Survey, box DG18
Results of a Survey for the Market for Travel to the U.S. in Japan box DG15
Resumption of Overseas Buying box IL1
Retail Audit: Principles and Practices box SR2
Retail Display and Packaging box SR2
Retail Shopping Areas box DG9
Retailing in the Seventies box IL3
Retail-Unit box IO8
Review and Summary of the Published Literature on Eating Out box DO1
Review for Lever Brothers Company of the Independent Buying and/or Barter Services and JWT's Buying and Barter Service, box DG17
Review of Recent Advertising Aiding the War Effort box DG10
Rhapsody in Red box DO4 (RESTRICTED)
Rhapsody in Red II box DO4 (RESTRICTED)
Roadmap of Greenland box IL9 (RESTRICTED)
Role of a New Brand Venture Group Within JWT Amsterdam box IO8
Role of Account Management at JWT Chicago, box DO1
Round the Woman box SR2
Rural Hyderabad box IO5
Ryukyuan Market box DG15
Sales Curves of New Products box IL2
Salute to the Stars box IO5
Samuel Yellin Cellini Wrought Iron box DG16
Sample Product and Brand Tables box SR1
Sampling Shops box SR2
Securities Exchange Act of 1934 box DG9
Selected Articles on Setting Adversiting Goals and Measuring Results box IO2
Self Service in Great Britain boxes IL1, SR2
Selling Abroad box DG9
Selling at Home box DG9
Selling from the Corporate Point of View, box DG20
Selling The Most Effective, Distinctive Advertising in the Marketplace box DG27 (RESTRICTED)
Sermons on Advertising box DG5
Simmons box SR5
Simmons-Scarborough Pamphlet box SR5
Simmons Study of Media and Markets box SR5
Simmons Teenage Research Study box SR5
Six Things Most Ad Agencies Would Never Say to a Client box DO2
Sixty-Four Problems box SR2
Social Change in Britain by 1984 box IL1
Social Class Definitions in Market Research: Objectives and Practice box SR2
Social Class in Sample Surveys box SR2
Society of Illustrators Catalog box SR5
Some Advertising Responsibilities in a Dynamic Society box DG11
Some Observations On Forecasting and Planning, box IL4
Some Things We Have Learned box DG12
Some Things We Have Learned About Building Client Relationships box DG27 (RESTRICTED)
Some Things We Have Learned About Managing a JWT Office boxes DG20, DG24, DG26 (RESTRICTED)
Some Things We Learned About Launching Mindshare box SR6 (RESTRICTED)
Sources of Information on European Countries, box IL3
South African Clients box IO10
South African Market box DG15
Southern African Intelligence: General Market Report No. 47 box IO10
Special Markets Group: The Black Consumer Market box DG18
Spot Buying at J. Walter Thompson box DG17
Standards for Report Typing boxes DO1, DO2
Statement to the JWT-Japan Creative Staff/Wilson Siebert box DG17
Statistical Accuracy of IPA NRS Results, box SR2
Statistical Overview of the South African Market box IO10
Strategic Concept of Consumer Involvement: It's Importance Today box IO4
Studio Sull'Immagine delle Reti Televisive, box IO6
Study of Media and Markets "RPC" Levels, box SR5
Subscriber Lists box SR5
Successful Examples of 'Mass Education' by Clients of J. Walter Thompson C. box OV1
Surprise 1988 Forecast box DG21
Survey of American Consumers box SR1
Switchback to Confidence box IO2
Symposium in Commemoration of the 25th Anniversary of JWT Japan box IO6
Target Group Index box SR2
Target Group Index Plan box SR1
Target Panel box SR2
Target Teen Index box SR1
Technical Plan box SR1
Technique for Producing Ideas boxes DG13, DG22, DG24 (RESTRICTED)
Techniques in Market Forecasting box IL2
Tele Communications boxes DG19, DO2
Television Attention Research box IL1
Television In Europe box IL4
Television in Latin America box DG15
Television Today- Television Tomorrow box IL7
Testing Television Commercials box DG14
Theoretical Case for Professionalism (part 1 &2) box IO10
Things We Have Learned About Employee Attitude Surveys box DG19
Things to Know about Trade-Marks box DG7
This Is Argentina box IO1
Thomas Francis Sutton box DG19
Thompson box OV1
Thompson Blue Book on Advertising boxes DG5-DG7
Thompson Consumer Index of Markets box IO5
Thompson Office Manager's Handbook box DG22
Thompson Recruitment Advertising box DG22
Thompson Red Book on Advertising boxes DG4, DG27 (RESTRICTED)
Thompson Redbook box IL6
Thompson Rural Market Index box IO5
Thompson Total Branding (4 booklets) box DG26 (RESTRICTED)
Thompson Total Branding Guidebook box DG26 (RESTRICTED)
Thompson Way box IO6
Thompson Way Handbook boxes DG21, DG27 (RESTRICTED)
Thompson's Battery of Magazines box DG2
Thompson's Pocket Speller boxes DG2, DG3
Three Myths About Our Export Trade box IL2
Tihama box SR5
Times box IL1
Tips on Type box DG15
To Speak As Well As You Think box DG19
Today's TV Market box DG12
Tomorrow's Consumer box IL3
Tomorrow's Food box IL3
Tool Kit--Advertising Planning Methods box DG21
Tourism Research in Japan box DG15
T-Plan boxes DO2, IL2
Training and Professional Development in the European Region box IO12 (RESTRICTED)
Transformation box DG25 (RESTRICTED)
Treasurer, the Stockholder and the Customer, box DG9
Trends and Retail Sales 1966-1975 box IL5
Trends in Magazine Audiences box SR1
Trouble at Credibility Gap box DG17
TV Fact Book boxes DG21-DG25 (RESTRICTED)
TV Terminology box DG13
TV Violence: In the Eyes of the Beholders, box DG18
TV/Radio Schedule box DG13
Una Téchnica para Producir Ideas box IO8
Unconventional Wisdom box DG21
Under New Management boxes DG18, DG19
Understanding Buyer Behavior boxes DG18, DG19
Unified International Practices box IO2
United States Stamps box DG16
Upbeat box SR6 (RESTRICTED)
Up Front, vol. 3 box SR6 (RESTRICTED)
U.S. Clients box DG26 (RESTRICTED)
U.S. Coffee Market box DG21
U.S. Commercial Television 1950-1975 box DG17
U.S. Consumer Media box DG22
USA Market for Overseas Goods boxes DG11, DG13
Use and Abuse of Survey Research in Advertising Regulation box DG18
Validity of Test Marketing box IL2
Vienna Presents box IO2
Viewdata box IL7
Viewers' Choice: The Value of Higher Ratings, box SR5
Visualize: Sharing Resources box IL8
Visualize: The Internet box IL9 (RESTRICTED)
Walter Thompson de Mexico S.A. box IO8
We are Ready to Meet Change with Change, box DG17
We've Made Our Move in Detroit box DO2
Welcome to JWT- Sue Dean box IO2
Werbelächer: Muß das sein? box SR1
West Coast's Marketing Opportunities box DG11
West Germany--A Lost Opportunity? box IL2
Western Europe box SR3
Western European Markets box DG13
What Do These Changes Mean? box DG8
What Do We Know About How Advertising Works? box IL2
What Has Happened to the Advertising Dollar? box IO3
What I Had To Do box DG27 (RESTRICTED)
What is a Brand? box IL3
What is Advertising? box DG21
What is Marketing? box IL1
What JWT Stands For box DG19
What Magazine Advertising is Accomplishing, box DG7
What Others Really Think About Account Managers, box DG22
What Puts the Prices Up? box IL2
What Say The Augurers? box IL2
What's New from the Corporate Point of View, box SR3
Where Good Advertising is the Constant Product, box DG4
Where the TV Sets Are box DG12
Where They Live box DG9
Who We Are (Hill & Knowlton) box SR4
Who's Who box OV5
Who-What-Why-When-Where of Public Relations, box DG22
Why Work for a Living? (London) box IL7
Why Work for a Living? (New York) box DO2
Will Advertising Need Smaller Targets and Better Gun-Sights? box IL2
Willkommen bei J. Walter Thompson box IO4
Wine Consumer Survey box DG12
Winner's Manual... box IL6
Women in the 90s- A New Age in Marketing to Women box IO4
Women's Use of Media box IL5
Womenscope box DG20
Working Smarter Through Better Time Management, box SR4
Working Wire box SR6 (RESTRICTED)
World Business box DG16
World Markets for U.S. Exports box DG10
World of Demand box DG16
World-Wide Opportunities for Better Living Standards box IL1
Worldwide White Pea Awards box DG25 (RESTRICTED)
WTM en Mexico box IO8
Xpedite! box SR4
Year in View boxes DG26-DG27 (RESTRICTED)
Year One of the People Meter box DG21
Yearbook (JWT Chicago) box DO2
Yes--But What Responses? box DG19
Zap Proof box DG20
Advertising -- Spain -- 20th century; Research reports and papers; Corporation reports; Advertising -- France -- 20th century; Advertising -- Germany -- 20th century; Advertising -- India -- 20th century; Advertising -- South Africa -- 20th century; Advertising -- Great Britain -- 20th century; Advertising -- Australia -- 20th century; Advertising -- Belgium -- 20th century; Advertising -- Canada -- 20th century; Advertising agencies -- History; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Advertising -- United States -- 20th century; Advertising -- United States -- 19th century; Marketing research; Publications; Advertising agencies -- Great Britain; Advertising agencies -- Great Britain -- History; Lord, Geller, Federico, Einstein, Inc.; Simmons Market Research Bureau; Hill & Knowlton, Inc.; J. Walter Thompson Company. Atlanta Office; Brouillard Communications, Inc.; British Market Research Bureau, Ltd; J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Detroit Office; J. Walter Thompson Company; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; J. Walter Thompson Company. San Francisco Office
- Corporate Publications Series (Restricted), 1918-2005, 36 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes directories, client lists, financial reports and other publications that pertain to corporate operations. Organized into seven subseries--Worldwide Office Address Lists, Client Lists, Financial and Stockholder Reports, JWT Group Reports, Worldwide Office Fact Books, Profile Books and Telephone Directories. Most reports in this series are periodically issued; thus, files are arranged by type or title, and chronologically therein.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restriction Note: Materials less than fifteen years old, other than advertisements, are closed to non-JWT users. Individual boxes are so marked. Where items have been removed and relocated to Restricted Materials, that item has been replaced by a dummy folder indicated by a title in brackets.
  - Address Lists, Worldwide Offices, 1966-1991
    - 1966-1991, 7 folders (Box CA1)
  - Address Lists, Worldwide Offices, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1992-2005
    - 1992-1993, 10 folders (Box CA2)
    - 1993-1998, 15 folders (Box CA3)
    - 1998-2001, 11 folders (Box CA4)
    - 2002-2005, 11 folders (Box CA5)
  - Client Lists, 1917-2005
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - Client Gain and Loss Reports
      - Client losses, 1960-1985 (Box CC1)
      - Domestic clients lost, 1960-1986 (Box CC1)
      - Gains and losses, 1982, 2 folders (Box CC1)
      - International account gains and losses, 1984-1987, 3 folders (Box CC1)
      - Worldwide gains and losses, 1988-1991, 7 folders (Box CC2)
    - Domestic Clients
      Arranged alphabetically, and chronologically therein.
      - Domestic client lists
        - 1918, 1927-1974, 21 folders (Box CC3)
        - 1975-1981, 11 folders (Box CC4)
        - 1981-1983, 9 folders (Box CC5)
        - 1984-1986, 10 folders (Box CC6)
        - 1986-1991, 6 folders (Box CC7)
      - North America client index, undated (Box CC7)
      - Red Book entries, 1917-1980, 3 folders (Box CC7)
    - Domestic Clients, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1992-2005
      - Domestic client lists
        - 1992-2005, 5 folders (Box CC8)
    - International Clients
      - International client lists, 1925-1996 (1993-1996 Removed to International Clients, Restricted Materials, box CC10), 10 folders (Box CC9)
      - Top 20 clients (international and domestic), 1984-1985 (Box CC9)
      - [Worldwide active clients, 1997-1998, Removed to International Clients, Restricted Materials, box CC10] (Box CC9)
    - International Clients, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1993-1998
      - International client lists, 1993-1996, 2 folders (Box CC10)
      - Worldwide active clients, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box CC10)
    - Subsidiaries' Client Lists
      - EA International, 1981 (Box CC11)
      - Hill & Knowlton, 1983 (Box CC11)
      - Lord, Geller, Federico, Einstein, 1978-1983, 2 folders (Box CC11)
    - Uniform Account Lists
      - 1962-1968, 8 folders (Box CC12)
      - 1969-1976, 8 folders (Box CC13)
      - 1977-1984, 8 folders (Box CC14)
      - 1984-1987, 7 folders (Box CC15)
      - 1988-1991, 6 folders (Box CC16)
    - Uniform Account Lists, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1992-1994
      - 1992-1994, 3 folders (Box CC17)
  - Corporate Identity Plan Records, 1997-1998; 3 Linear Feet
    - Audit report, 1997 (Box CIP1)
    - Billing, 1997 (Box CIP1)
    - Brief, 1997 (Box CIP1)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box CIP1)
    - Correspondence--Internal, 1997-1998 (Box CIP1)
    - Correspondence--Partners, 1997 (Box CIP1)
    - Expressing the Power of the JWT Brand, 1997 (Box CIP1)
    - Invoices, 1997-1998 (Box CIP1)
    - J. Walter Thompson Guidelines, undated (Box CIP1)
    - JWT Identity Guidelines, 1997 (Box CIP2)
    - Launch book, 1997 (Box CIP2)
    - Letter, business cards, 1997 (Box CIP2)
    - "Local Knowledge" design examples, undated (Box CIP2)
    - Manual, 1997 and undated; 3 folders (Box CIP2)
    - Manual, 1997 and undated; 2 folders (Box CIP3)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 2 folders (Box CIP3)
    - Powerpoint, DPT designs, 1997 (Box CIP3)
    - Print materials examples, undated (Box CIP3)
    - Powerpoint examples, 1997 (Box CIP4)
    - Proposed Revisions to JWT Corporate Identity Proposal, undated (Box CIP4)
    - J. Walter Thompson Worldwide visual identity, 1997 (Box CIP5)
    - Visual identity presentation, foamcore mounted, undated (Box CIP5)
  - Financial and Stockholder Reports, 1950, 1969-1987
    Arranged alphabetically by report title and chronologically therein.
    - Annual Reports, 1969-1986 (Box CF1)
    - Annual 10-K Reports, 1969-1986 (Box CF2)
    - Notice of special meeting of stockholders, 1950 (Box CF3)
    - Prospectus, 1969, 2 folders (Box CF3)
    - Proxy statements, 1970-1987, 18 folders (Box CF3)
  - JWT Group Reports, 1981-1987
    - Annual Objectives and Profit Targets, 1981 (Box CJ1)
    - Annual Report, 1981-1986, 5 folders (Box CJ1)
    - Directors Report on Coverage of Events, 1987 Jan. 26-Feb. 27, 2 folders (Box CJ1)
      Analysis of media coverage of WPP's takeover of JWT.